Infe Exploration Time! Infe exploration time!
Dharma, Hinano and Torine members!
Pleased to meet you.
I'm K.
P
Please.
I don't think we have anything at all.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Today, you two are here.
Today, right?
I'd like you two to...
What are you going to do?
I'll tell you what they're going to do.
You piss me off.
I'm going to say this for a while longer, Hinano.
It's like you came here today.
What do you want me to do?
Why are you talking to the director?
Because I'm going to accept it.
What are you going to do?
I'll tell you what we're going to do.
Today's exploration...
Let's power up your in-building standees!
Standby in the museum
Standby in the museum.
Yes!
Yes, yes, yes!
Standby
Standby.
Inside the pavilion.
Standee.
Inside the building.
You're boring live, aren't you?Boring live show, you.
You're lyrics are so thin.
In-house standby
It's an exploration to power up the
This is an expedition
What's this all about?
What is it?
Now, right now, suddenly Tohoku-san
The 3rd mini-album
THE TOHOKU has just been released!
Yes, sir.
The jacket animation
You have it, don't you?
The standee of it
Standby...
Eeveens.
Standee? Standby?
Why do they play that song for the encore?
Is that all you have?
Forget it.
That's Eevees.
On the stairwell.
The landing? Standee?
Standee?
Standee.
On the landing at ebean's.
It's on display on the dance floor.
Every floor.
All of you.
Standees.
May I introduce you?
We have your third mini-album.
The illustration on the jacket.
This is a life-size version of it.
It's on display on each floor.
Standee.Standee.
So let's take that dance floor.
Let's power up today!
We're going on an expedition.
How?
I'd like you two to draw, write...
I'd like you to write something on it.
I'd like to hang it next to the standee.
I see.
Okay, let's see what you've got.
Let's go take a look at their corner.
Let's go take a look.
Let's see what it looks like.
Standee, let's go take a look.
Can you see it?
Okay.
What the hell? What have we become?
Let me just bring them back one more time.
Se-no!
Whoo!
Yes, we're on the ninth floor!
Oh, my gosh! It's bigger than a toy!
So cute!
I thought the Kitami Zone was on the 9th floor.
Yes, that's right.
It's pretty big.
I asked Mr. London to draw a cute illustration.
I see.
Did you have any orders for this? Or...
Oh, there was an order.
An order? Yes, yes.
Really?
Really.
I had told them about the neckline and the hair, and now it's done.
I was so excited about the ribbons, no matter how hard I worked on them.
Purple and light blue, I was into it then, but the combination.Purple and light blue, I was into it at the time, and then the combination.
That's why I asked for those shades and pinkish makeup.
You're talking out of your ass!
I don't understand!
That must have been a lot of work.
Also, everyone's name is definitely in there.
I didn't tell them this.
Oh, really.
That's why everyone's name is in the picture, too.
I see.
Kinami is displayed on the ninth floor.
I'm going to power this up today, and I'm going to put something on the side.
Draw something of Kinami or something, and power it up.
YES!
This is me.
Hinano-san is on the second floor.
The landing of the third floor from the second floor
Three-half
This was written by a person named Peppermint.
I see, it's cute!
I was really surprised that Peppermint-san could write it because she liked it so much.
I was really surprised.
I didn't really order it, but
I didn't really order it, but it's Patsy's and the color is purple like this.
It's not purple, but...
I wanted it to be a normal color, not purple.
That's what I wanted.
I also like Peppermint's color.
I want to leave it all up to you.
I see.
You wanted me to look like Peppermint.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
That's all I need to know.
I told him I'd take care of everything else.
And he put a bear on it.
Oh, my God, it's true!Oh, it's true.
I didn't say that.
You followed me.
You put a bear on me.
And I really like the tempo of Ms. Peppermint.
I really like it.
I said, "I want to have 10.
and he gave it to me.
I have the name here.
That's right.
Hina no.
I see. It's cute.
Cute.
Hinano-san...
This is the second floor landing.
Let me power it up.
Yes, ma'am.
Hina-san.
Yes, sir.
Huh? Rinne-san.
Hinano-san.
Yes, ma'am.
Sakura-san
Yes.
Ms. Kitami
Yes
Mr. Picasso
Yes.
What do you mean?
I'm going to ask you to draw a picture now.
I'd like you to draw something here in front of me that you both designed.
We'll hang it next to the person you just saw.
The theme is up to you.
For now, let's make the dance floor more powerful.
Let's start painting.
I'm looking forward to it!I'm looking forward to it.
You write?
I'm not writing.
Why art club?
You were in art club?
Yes, I'm in the art club.
You're a force to be reckoned with.
Me too.
Well, I was in the art club of the North Ward and Yunano.
Yes, me too.
There's no such thing.
There's no Kitakyushu section and Yunano's.
The art club and Yuna's club in Kitakyushu?
That's the Kitakyushu section.
Kitaku-bu?
I've told you several times.
Don't move your mouth.
Can I ask you to move your hand?
Look! Surprise!
Hinao, you're surprisingly careful. I thought you were the type of person who wouldn't draft something like that.
I thought you were the type to go boldly. I heard that you draft these things.
I heard that you draft them. No, no, I don't need that kind of boldness.
Yay!
Do you want me to put it on?
No, thanks.
Oh, I want to bottle it! With this!
Let me try one!
No, I don't want to do it once. I mean...
If you're gonna do it once, do it 10 times! Oh, God!
Oh, okay?
That's what I'm talking about!
It's an example.
Like, from the front.
Write it down!
What do we do now?
What are you going to do today? You've been talking like that for a while now.What are you going to do today? He said something like...
There's something like this for sumo wrestlers, right?
Like handprints.
People who come to see it...
I can match it with the size of the handprint.
I'm sure.
Wow!
That's great!
What would you like me to draw?
Oh! You're talking to me!
You're talking to me!
You look like an artist!
What's he saying?
You decide!
Oh, he's a bit of an oraganic guy.
Oh, my God!
You want to draw a circle?
That's a good idea.
Maybe something will come out of it.
Okay, then!
Team!
I'm going to draw a line on the top of the stone.
I'm going to make something.
I see!
I'll draw it with my eyes glazed over!
See you in the next video!
Bye bye!
Yes, ma'am.
You are going to create it now, aren't you?
So this is where it all starts to come together.
At the moment, it's just a doodle.
It's really just a child's doodle.
I may have failed.
Can you please stop saying "failure" with such bravado?
It's for decoration.
I might have really failed.I might have really screwed up.
Don't tell me.
Oh! Something!
Everything's fine!
It's okay!
It's okay, it's okay!
It's gonna be fun! I'm having mine!
It's amazing!
Like graffiti art.
It's fun!
I love this kind of thing, don't you?
I'm looking forward to seeing it finished.
Finished, Hina-san?
I think I might be in.
It's Punksy, isn't it? This is totally Punksy!
Help!
What's wrong?
It's like an art explosion.
I don't think it's enough. You know, that draft you wrote with your eyes closed.
It's probably not enough.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Can I be bolder?
Oh, that's good, that's good, that's good.
Oh!
But this is just the kind of artwork you'd expect from an artist like this.
Yeah. It's like a work of art, depending on who paints it.
Your brush is starting to run.
Art is an explosion!
What kind of image are you working on now?
Is it a butterfly? This one.
If that's what you think, then maybe.
Artistic.
It pops. I just let my hand go where it will.
That's cool. What do you two have to say for yourselves?
What do you mean? Everything you say sounds like an artist.
There's something meaningful about this black butterfly.This black butterfly seems to have a meaning.
I think she's still moping.
That's all I'm saying.
It's turning out to be a great contrast, isn't it?
I like it. It kind of looks like Nike.
It kind of looks like Nike.
When the shape of your face is your name.
Yes, sir.
Rinne Rinne Temple, right?
Like a henohenomohe temple.
Yes, exactly.
I'm getting afraid to look next door.
I'm afraid to shake the camera.
I'll just look at it for a second.
Oh, look out!
I'm gonna take a look.
Oops.
He just wanted to paint it light blue.
I'm worried about her.
I'm worried about her mental state.
I wonder if she'll be okay.
Look out! We're being pulled in.
I'm being sucked into a black hole right now.
They both have their own personalities.
They're so different.
Even if I told you to power up the same place...
But the result is totally different.
That's art, isn't it?
Mr. Ito.
I like this.
Kitami's face is used as the name.
It has originality and character.
Okay, I've finished Rine's work.
It's done!
So cute!Cute
Awesome pop!
I like it. Linepo has a great sense of style.
Do you have a title or something for this picture?
Welcome
I made it with the image of a welcome board.
It looks like something you'd see at a wedding.
I made this board with the word "welcome" in English.
Welcome!
Welcome.
This is really nice!
The members' faces are the letters of their names.
It's so cute.
The top is hand painted with paint.
And there's handprints. Handprints are cute.
I've always wanted to try it. You can see how big the hands are.
Look at this. Look at the size of the back hand.
If you come see this, we can match them up. I'm pretty big.
That's a great welcome.
This will be on the ninth floor. Thank you very much.
And now...
Hinano-san, right?
The title is...
Encounter with Michi.
So cool!
Cool. Deep meaning.
You mean it's not a butterfly?
It's like a Michi creature.
Butterfly. Butterfly?
Is it a butterfly? It's poisonous, but the color around it smells sweet, like a poisonous butterfly.
It's so cherry blossom Picasso.
I'm a cherry blossom Picasso!
I expressed "e-beans".
It represents e-beans!I was expressing eBeans.
You're expressing eeveens? Hiccup, that's amazing. That's what I was looking at.
If you come and take a look at it, you'll see...
But if you come and take a look at it, you'll see that they used some kind of technology that looks like that... like spray.
There's something like a spray, you see?
Look, it's wonderful.
So this painting by Hicasso will be displayed on the landing from the second floor to the third floor?
Yes. Thank you. Thank you very much.
In addition to the two artists' works, we'll make a message board.
I'll make one for guests to write messages on.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes. You're going to write butterflies? Do you mean...
You're going to write that butterfly? Tiny. Wow, it's real.
Real butterflies!
Okay, okay, so the message board that you two just wrote is going to be on the 5th floor.
I hope you will write something on it when you come to the show.
They are both so cute!
They are so cute! The combination of these two is pretty cute too!
I didn't think there would be one.
I am honored to be able to do this.
This is the one here,
This video was released
I hope you all enjoy it,
Please take a picture with Standee.
I hope you will come and see it,
I hope you will come and see it.
Also, I wrote a yosegaki on the wall.
I wrote "ayasukibe" on the wall,
Please write a lot.
That's all for today's Takie timer.
That's all for now.
Thank you very much, captain.
Thank you very much.
Thank you all very much.Thank you all very much.
Bye-bye.